If you are not in combat getting shot
at, I do not want to hear about your
military service. You joined the gym.
Everyone in my generation
was damaged
irreparably
by growing up with minivans. Most of
your Disney World trip will be having to
explain to your children why they are
waiting on a line with mostly morbidly
obese adults to go on the ride. I'm
funnel cake dad.
I want to talk about this Costco family
before I get out of here because
you know it's so interesting. This
Costco family is taking the world by
storm. No, we don't know anything. Oh
god, please let me prepare myself before
this starts just happening. Um,
>> it's not plain. It's not played. No,
it's by the way, everything that I
thought like the country would turn
into, it's somehow worse. And I like I'm
like hyperbolic. Like I like you look at
listen my old [__] It's like it's like
everything's dialed up to an 11 and
we're at like a 13 in this country right
now. So I don't even know what these
people are or who they are, but they are
kind of interesting and you can't stop
watching them, but it is something's
like crazy and wrong.
And they're this family. They're like
Costco influencers and the dad they got
to meet like Gary Vee and the dad's like
the dad goes I've been following Gary
Vee for 10 years. The dad's clearly been
trying to get famous forever. Okay. And
and he goes, I've been following Gary
Vee for 10 years and he's like really
responsible for this. And I'm like don't
even blame this on Gary Vee. Like
there's no way that Gary Vee even
cosigned this. Like if this guy went to
Gary Vee and was like, "So I'm just
gonna look at the camera go double CHUNK
CHOCOLATE COOKIE." I think Gary Vee
would even go, "Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe you should do something else." I
think Gary Vee would even go like,
"Maybe that's not the way to do it."
Double talk.
Like there's no way that Gary Vee, for
all his craziness, co-signed any of
this.
This is a complete accident here.
Can you get one up where they dance?
>> Uh, yeah. Give me a sec.
>> Is YouTube or somebody gonna is are we
going to get in trouble for playing the
song Bring the Boom?
>> Why is it good? Is it because we want
death? Like we long for death in this
like, you know what I mean? Like I'm
like, why is this kind of entertaining?
Is it like is it like we just want this
civilization to crumble as quickly as
possible? I think that's what it is.
It's like the ultimate just like well it
cuz I watch this I'm not nearly as
disturbed by it as I should be. I just
kind like you end up kind of just we
BRING THE BOOM AND I go is it just a
it's the By the way it's the darkest
thing I have ever seen. There is nothing
darker than this. No, I'm ser I'm
serious. There is nothing darker than
this. WE BRING THE BOOM AND HAVE to the
cookies going like this. The fact that
this is kind of entertaining
signifies we are at the end. We are post
any type of like we are postpartum, we
are postmortem like we are done here. I
watch this stuff and I'm watching them
and I'm watching they do the we bring
the boom and they're eating these
cookies and these things and I'm like
why? This doesn't shock me. It doesn't
disturb me. It simply is a curiosity.
But I think what it is and I think the
reason for its popularity is we long now
kind of openly for some type of nuclear
holocaust or a natural dis like a major
natural dis. Like there's nothing else
that I can glean from the popularity of
this other than people are fully
subconsciously or consciously wishing
for like a black hole to swallow up the
universe. Can you please play more of
this?
>> YOUR FAVORITE FATHER AND SON
>> EVERY ON
this is why we fought THE IRAQ WAR. HOW
THE WHOLE EARTH.
>> GET THE WIZLER. I DON'T WANT GET THE
RIZZLER, PLEASE.
>> You know, the Rizzler's going to jail
one day. Like, it's going to be they're
going to be like social media star known
as the Rizzler was apprehended after a
fight with his girlfriend in the
Cheesecake Factory.
I can't understand
any of this. There we go. Here he is.
The Rizzler is the whole thing really. I
mean, the other two are great, but the
Rizzler is the thing
>> or a DOUBLE CHUNK CHOCOLATE COOKIE.
>> UM, I'M going to have to give the
chicken bake, the boom, and the double
chunk chocolate
a d.
>> You heard it from the wrestler.
>> I never had one of these before.
>> Now, let me just let Can I just ask you
a question? What happens next in
society?
You know what I mean? Like like what
exactly would be next here? What is act
two to this? Like what does this like
foretell you know? Like this is a it's
just look at the face. Can you zoom in
on the on the chunk chocolate cookie
guy's face? What? This guy is going to
kill them all Chris Benois style.
THERE'S NO WAY HE doesn't kill this
whole family. He's going to bring the
boom. All right. All right. Get him out
of here. I like them though. I do like
them. I WHY DO I LIKE THEM? And you this
other thing with schools where we've
talked about it on the program.
This California Senate approves ban on
transgender notification policies in
schools. I don't think it's good that
teachers and students keep secrets from
parents. I think that leads to a bad
place.
You know,
can you imagine Tim Walls being like,
"Listen, I know you want to chop your
tits off, and I support that, but why
don't you show them to me one time? Why
don't you show them to me one time
before you chop them off?" How great
would it come out if Tim Walsh,
he's just a folksy social studies
teacher, and he just fathered a child
with one of his students. just a folksy
I respect. He gets my vote if he comes
out and he goes, "We'll burn this
country down. We'll burn it down. We
burned it down once and we'll burn IT
DOWN AGAIN."
AND IF YOUR KID WANTS TO CHOP THEIR TITS
OFF, I'M COMING TO THE HOUSE WITH A
CLEAVER.
I'm funnel cake dad. He's angry. HE'S
ALWAYS ANGRY ABOUT I'M ANGRY, YOU
BASTARDS.
HE'S PISSED OFF BECAUSE him and his wife
have NO [__] MONEY. I'M MAD.
JD Vance, he didn't serve in THE
NATIONAL GUARD LIKE I BY THE WAY, THE
NATIONAL GUARD. Can we cut that out? THE
NATIONAL GUARD. I think I'm in the
National Guard.
I mean, the National Guard is nothing.
If you are not if you are not in combat
getting shot at, I do not want to hear
about your military service. You joined
a gym.
If you were in the National Guard and
you did not see f or if you're JD Vance
and you went to Iraq, you joined a gym
or even worse you were a journalist. I
do not want to hear about your military
service. If you were not getting shot, I
want you for me to take you seriously.
If I ask you about your service, you
have to look down because you've lost so
many people.
I've had friends
that came home from the military and
those friends tell me, they go, "Tim,"
and I swear to God they say this, they
go, "I did all these tours in Iraq and
the only way I can come now is even
though I have a wife, I get on a bed and
I put an ad on Craigslist and someone
comes in and they [__] me with a gun to
my head and I put a bag over my head and
then they leave and I never see them."
And that's that's I can come without
even touching my dick because that's how
[__] up they are. That's what I want
to hear from a candidate who did a bunch
of tours in the military. I don't want
if you are not that level of [__] up.
I don't believe you served. I don't
believe you served. I had someone tell
me that once. I go, I just take an ad
out on Craigslist. I get on all fours on
the bed. The guy comes in, [__] me in
the ass. I have a bag over my head. He
puts a gun to my head.
Why are you laughing? THIS IS WHAT
SOMEBODY SAID TO ME ONCE AT a lunch at
Hillstone. And I and I went, "Oh." And
he goes, "And then that person leaves
and I don't know who it was and I don't
know and I never see them again. And
then I get tested for AIDS. If you are
not at this is what I this is what I
believe because when you are in war,
things happen. It unlocks things. I
would do great in war. GREAT. I WOULD
DO. I JUST CAN'T be in the physicality
of it because I think it's like seems
tiring and stuff. But I would be great
at just the kind of decision making
uh you know just like they go we got to
kill we got to burn that village. I go
burn it baby. I would be able to give
the soldiers speeches to keep them on
message. You know people that are losing
heart soldiers that are losing heart.
They've killed too many kids and they
need somebody to come in and boost the
morale. You bring in Timmy. Timmy tells
you what to do. I know you're all
killing kids and it gets depressing, but
we got a bigger message. Bluechu is a
unique online service that delivers the
same active ingredients as
take all that money that we're funding
Israel with and give it to Candace Owens
so she can fight her lawsuit against
Breijit
Mcronone and Emanuel Mcronone. Andy,
here's what I'm saying.
Show the puss. Show the puss. Show the
[__]
And I'm not trying to be a problem. And
you know I never am. Show the puss. Show
the [__] I'm not saying she was born a
man. I don't know. There's a very easy
way to to put this to bed.
Number one, have Breijit Mcronone go on
the Neelk podcast
and have her show the [__] to what are
their names? Kyle and Steiny. Have her
show the [__] Take the out on the Neelk
podcast. Breed Mcronone.
Put your bush in Kyle from Neelk's face
and let's get justice. How about
justice?
Even people starving in Gaza want to
know this.
Even the starving children in Gaza want
to see where IS THE [__] LET'S PLAY A
LITTLE BIT of Candace. You're responding
to this
uh uh lawsuit from uh Breijit and
Emmanuel McCron.
>> You were born a man and you will die a
man. That's the point I'm making. So
give us a
>> By the way, I wish my father said that
to me at like any point in my life.
I wish I had that kind of support in my
own household. You were born a man.
You're a goddamn man. What?
Um,
we have Candace Owens here. She's being
sued by Breijit Mcronone is the first
lady of France.
And Candace has said Breijit
is a was born a gentleman.
And now I have challenged Breijit to go
on the Neelk boys podcast and show her
[__]
and let's do this thing.
End the war in Gaza. Show your Bush.
Show your [__] to the Neelk boys. You're
the you're the first lady of France. If
you're afraid to show your to Steiny
from Neelk, then you don't get to be the
first lady of France. You You don't get
to be it.
Show your to Joe Rogan in his studio.
FLY TO AUSTIN and open your spread your
legs for Joe Rogan. Hey, Mom. That's
weird, Mom.
Well, it could it could definitely be
worked on, Mom. It could It's It Well,
it's [__] man. It could definitely be.
Oh, 100%. It could absolutely have been
altered. Yeah. Well, for sure. I saw her
put Show your to Joe Rogan in Austin,
Texas, and go see a show at the
mothership.
SHOW THE CLAN.
JUST DO IT. END THE SPECULATION. SHOW
THE GASH.
This is politics.
It's the news and this is what has to
happen. We got to move on as a society
from this war in Gaza and from this.
Stop starving the children in Gaza. Show
your [__] to Joe Rogan. Go on. Kill
Tony. I'm the president of France's
WIFE. AND THEY SAY, "I GOT A [__] BUT I
GOT A CLIT." BOOM. RED Band does a sound
effect. Make the podcast rounds and show
everyone your puss, please. The death of
the minivan. It was a perfect vehicle.
Uh, no, it was not. The minivan dilemma.
It is the least cool vehicle ever
designed, yet the most useful, offering
the best value for the most. The
minivan, by the way, destroyed uh
everyone I know's life.
The minivan immediately became like,
this is why everyone in my generation
did not have a clean house until they
had to go to therapy for years. Their
parents had this mobile
garbage uh trash compactor called a
minivan that we all were driven around
in where when we were children, we would
fling dunkaroos and Milano cookies and
fun dip and we would throw them all over
this car. And they had like those felt
seats or whatever, you know, that uh
that cushion seat and it was like a the
weird velvet and it was always sticky
with [__] It looked like that.
Everyone in my generation
was damaged
irreparably
by growing up with minivans, eating in
them, fighting with your brothers and
sisters and friends in them, having your
parents. It was all part of going
through a drive-thru, eating the food,
throwing the food, and look at them.
This is this is the way they looked. And
that's why when my generation of people
went to college, their dorms were
disgusting. When they first got
girlfriends, their girlfriends went,
"What the [__] How are you raised?" And
they were raised in a minivan by boomers
that turned it into a disgusting
environment on wheels. The cars you grew
up in are the reason you're an animal.
They are.
And if you didn't grow up in a minivan
that's filthy, good for you.
But if you did, you're an animal. The
cars you grew up in, the cars that you
sat in the back of, that was your
example, okay, of what was tolerated and
what was not tolerated. There were
certain friends I had where the cars
were immaculate. Most not, but some. But
a lot of my close friends, because the
classes,
you know, don't really coingle. Most of
my lower middle class dirt bag friends
and their dirt bag families had minivans
and no one took any pride in a a minivan
was bought to be destroyed.
You hated it. You hated the fact that
you were in it.
It was a roving
garage of [__] and you would see them.
You would all you would get in line at
Wendy's and it would be minivan. My
mother had an econo line Ford van. The
minivan wasn't enough. She needed a big
van that had a bed in the back because
she would always go and get uh antiques.
She would pick up furniture that people
had left outside of their houses in the
hopes that she was going to refurbish
it.
But the minivan, I couldn't think of a
type of vehicle that did more damage to
people than the minivan.
Here's here's what the minivan did. It
made everybody a fatty boomdaddy. Number
one, you don't need that much space. You
don't you don't
you don't need that much space.
The minivan was so that you could go and
shop and buy crap, put it in the car.
You could go eat and put leftovers in a
car. Your kids could play with toys in
the car.
And everything that should have been
reserved for
a location that didn't move and wasn't
in traffic would be happening in the
car. You could eat in the car.
Everybody, here's your food. Everybody
eating the car. Everyone's covered in
ketchup. Great. Here's some napkins.
There's ketchup all over the thing. It's
sticky. It's filthy. It was the worst
car and it made the worst people. It
did. Anyone that grew up in a minivan
knows exactly what I'm talking about. My
grandparents never had a minivan. My
grandfather had a uh he had a Crown Vic.
He had a Cadillac Elorado. He had a
Crown Vic. Nobody ate in the car. You
did not eat in the car. You were not
allowed. As soon as the minivans came
around, not only were you allowed to eat
in the car, it was actually required.
That's why we GOT IT. WE GOT IT so you
could eat your fat stuff your fat FACE
IN THE CAR CUZ WE'RE ANIMALS. And we got
to eat on the way to practice for this
thing.
We got to eat on the way to karate. and
you can't fit in the belt that you're
not going toinging get upgraded to
anyway.
You would you would eat on the way to
thing. They would pick you up at school
in the minivan. You would go you would
eat and then they would take you to
wherever
and then they would uh you know drop you
off then pick you up. Eating eating
eating always dirty filthy toys in the
minivan. Play with these toys. Play
around.
It was a disgusting.
The minivan arrived way back when as a
savior when Chrysler under the former
Ford chief Leia Kok's direction first
conceived of the design in the late
1970s.
One was the land yacht style station
wagon perhaps avocado green with faux
wood paneling. Lots of kids could pile
into the bench and jump seats while the
rear storage accessible by hatch allowed
for easy loading. These cars were
somewhat functional but they didn't seem
that safe. The Suburban family's other
choice was the full-size van, a big boxy
transporter utility vehicle.
Chrysler's minivan would steer clear of
those two dead ends and carry American
families onto the open roads towards
well youth soccer and mall commerce. It
really did bring innovation. Ample
seating organized in rows with easy
access with the ability to stow those
seats in favor of a large cargo bay with
a set of sliding doors.
So everybody loved these things. Sales
reached 700,000 by the end of the decade
as the station wagon all but disappeared
and the minivan came in.
People lived in their cars. They ate in
their cars.
The nation where cars stood in for power
and freedom. The minivan would mean the
opposite. As a vehicle, it symbolized
the burdens of domestic life. This is
true. It's why you could treat it like
[__]
That's why the minivan you could treat
like [__] because it was a utility
vehicle. It was a vehicle to go
literally from point A to point B. You
weren't going to stop at the grocery
store and get food and go home and cook
it.
You were going to drive through a mobile
poison factory and kill your children on
the way to [__] dropping them off at
dance class so your fat daughter could
learn how to do a piouette.
No car represented the decline of this
empire more than the minivan. None. And
no car was beloved more uh by the boomer
than the minivan because they needed
space. Boomers needed space.
There it is.
The Chrysler Town and Country. Show that
one. That was the high-end one. Go to
the Chrysler Town and Country
Town and Country Chrysler. That's kind
of nice.
My aunt had that. This is the old one.
That's the old Chrysler. Town and
Country. People would pick you up with
that. They would pick you up at school
and they would sit you in that
and then they woulding douse you in
maple syrup
and then bring you to a [__] soccer
game.
It is crazy. If you're driving one of
those now it's like god. So what are
they being replaced by? Fentanyl SUVs,
right? I mean what's what's replacing
the minivans? Suicide. People just
checking out Disneyland
reporting fewer uh operating uh
operating profit in Q3 citing inflation
and demands for park as moderate. People
are not going to Disney World as much.
I'm very proud of my country even though
many of them are watching the Olympics.
I'm very proud of my country that they
are starting to see how disgusting
Disney World is, how repulsive it is. It
is terrible to bring your children to.
And this is not because they have gay
day or whatever that some of you
queueing on lunatics. It's because it is
benile. It is boring. Disney movies have
sucked now for many many years. Uh
they're no longer interesting. They
don't have villains. The the reason the
Disney movies suck now is they don't
have villains. They don't have
Maleficent. They don't have Ursula. They
don't teach anybody anything about the
world. They don't teach children about
the world anymore. Uh they are strange
and they're odd and they are not worth
anybody's time. And Disney World is old
and it's getting decrepit and many of
the people that are visiting Disney
World are mentally unstable adults. And
now because we have dstigmatized that
and we have allowed mentally unstable
adults to fill the parks, most of your
Disney World trip will be having to
explain to your children why they are
waiting on a line with mostly morbidly
obese adults to go on the ride. Why are
all the people on the RIDE BIG AND FAT?
MOMMY, because that's who comes here
now. Morbidly obese adults on multiple
medications. That's who attends the
park. WHY IS THE WHY IS IT such a long
wait? Well, because adults come here
now, and it's okay.
Disney is ca and I'm not even [__]
on my gals, my plus-sized park hoppers.
We love you. We love you ladies.
But most people are realizing that
Disney World is just not worth it. You
take your kids once. It is stressful out
there. You know, I'm doing a renovation
right now and
it is incredibly
trying.
I am at a breaking point. I am at a
breaking point
with Cedar
and all of these running, you know, I
was on a plane coming back to Los
Angeles. all of these shows, these uh
these shows about, you know, Flip This
House and uh Flip or Flop with the Tar
El Musa, whatever. They're all fake. And
all of these shows give you this idea
that you could just flip a house.
>> You could go in there and, you know,
switch out a few things and get
everything done on the cheap, turn it
around and flip it. it right now. The
cost of anything, if someone comes into
your home now and you just say, "Hey,
I I have a gaping hole in my wall. Can
you fix it?" By the after 3 minutes of
talking to them, you go, "We'll live
with it. We're going to live with it."
If there are wild animals
coming at night into your home to kill
your children and all you need is is a
wall patched. After 3 to five minutes of
speaking to somebody right now, you just
go, "Fuck it. You know what? It's not
that bad. We'll live with it. It's a
nice breeze." because the amount of
money that it costs to get anything
done, the materials,
you know, yes, sure, these are luxury
problems, but that's they're still
problems.
And they're not always luxury problems.
Some people the people are having babies
and they need bigger houses because now
because of Roie Wade, they have to have
them. So, they have to put on extensions
and it's [__] nuts out there.